I spring fans welcome to another
我春天的歌迷欢迎来到另一个
installment of spring tips in this
在此安装Spring 提示
installment we're gonna talk about
我们将要讨论的分期付款
reactive sequel based data access so of
基于反应性续集的数据访问
course if any of you have been following
当然，如果有人在关注
along we we're talking a lot about
我们一直在谈论很多
reactive programming of late and for
最近和之后的反应式编程
good reason because it gives us a way to
有充分的理由，因为它为我们提供了一种方法
describe potentially latent potentially
描述潜在的潜在
asynchronous input and output
异步输入和输出
asynchronous i/o and to provide a sort
异步I / O并提供一种
of wrapper types types that we can then
包装类型的类型，然后我们可以
use on top of that asynchronous i/o
在该异步I / O上使用
foundation to model the world to think
模拟世界思维的基础
about the world to think about the
关于世界的思考
integration between components in the
组件之间的集成
world and when we move to reactive
世界以及当我们转向被动时
programming when we move to asynchronous
我们转向异步编程
based programming we we need to be aware
基于程序的编程，我们需要注意
of the fact that data is potentially
数据潜在的事实
unlimited that data will be you know
无限的数据将是你知道的
that the bytes that we are sending on
我们正在发送的字节
the on a on a channel for example are
例如，频道上的
gonna be sent and we might get the
将被发送，我们可能会得到
acknowledgment later on and you know
确认之后，你知道
inversely that the data that we expect
相反，我们期望的数据
from a read may arrive in in a
从阅读中可能会到达
nanosecond it might matter you know I
十亿分之一秒，这可能很重要，您知道我
might just as well arrive in in a week
可能会在一周内到达
right it's asynchronous this latent it's
对，它是异步的，这是潜在的
a potentially unbounded as well there
还有一个潜在的无限
may be there might be a lot of it and so
可能有很多，所以
these these ideas make it so that we can
这些想法使我们能够
now write code that monopolizes threads
现在编写垄断线程的代码
as little as possible and the benefit of
尽可能少的好处
that is that we can move input and
那就是我们可以移动输入
output to the sort of a single Taiyo
输出到单个太阳
mechanism for your platform and that
您平台的机制
thing that that channel that that that
那个那个那个那个那个那个那个那个频道的东西
mechanism can handle the work of moving
机制可以处理移动工作
data back and forth across the buffers
跨缓冲区来回传输数据
and only when there's actually
而且只有当
processing to be done on the data do we
对数据进行处理
then get move back into a thread and the
然后回到线程，然后
reason this is so variables because
之所以这么多是因为
threads are expensive they take up a lot
线程很昂贵，它们占用很多
of actual RAM like resources in the
实际RAM之类的资源
computer they're hard to schedule
电脑，他们很难安排
efficiently right so it requires a lot
正确有效，所以需要很多
of input and output a lot of a lot of
输入和输出的很多很多
work really beyond the input and output
确实超出了输入和输出的范围
to use threads efficiently so we want to
有效地使用线程，所以我们想
repurpose our existing threads because
重新利用我们现有的线程，因为
they're precious and there there are a
他们很珍贵，那里有一个
few of them as often as possible
尽可能少地
asynchronous i/o and reactive
异步I / O和反应式
programming which builds upon
在此基础上进行编程
asynchronous i/o enable that
异步I / O启用
so people are excited about this they
所以人们对此感到兴奋
want to move to reactive programming and
想转向反应式编程
you know for a long time we've talked to
你知道我们很久以来一直在和
talk to people about how you have some
与人们谈论你如何拥有一些
options when it comes to persistence
关于持久性的选择
certainly right we've we've we've seen
当然，我们已经看到了
that the spring team has already debuted
The Spring Team 已经亮相
spring data and spring data Finchley and
Spring 数据和Spring 数据Finchley和
sorry spring data kay and greater have
抱歉， spring data 凯和更多
supported reactive data access options
支持的反应式数据访问选项
including options for Redis reactive
包括Redis反应式的选项
Redis reactive Couchbase reactive
Redis反应性Couchbase反应性
Cassandra and reactive MongoDB and these
Cassandra和反应式MongoDB以及这些
are not just in most cases not just
在大多数情况下不只是
reactive equivalents of what you have in
您所拥有的反应性等效物
the synchronous and blocking
同步和阻塞
alternatives no no instance I'm in in
替代品，没有我没有参加的实例
many cases you are actually given more
很多情况下，您实际上得到的更多
features because of the foundations of
功能的基础
the of the implementation being based on
实现的依据是
this asynchronous reactive driver that
这个异步反应驱动程序
we use instead so instead of using the
我们使用代替，而不是使用
synchronous and blocking driver that
同步和阻塞驱动程序
underpins for example the regular spring
例如常规Spring
data MongoDB we use a completely
数据MongoDB我们完全使用了
different driver which supports
支持的不同驱动程序
asynchronous i/o for the spring data
用于Spring 数据的异步I / O
reactive MongoDB driver and so we can do
反应性MongoDB驱动程序，所以我们可以做
some things that are just not as easy
有些事情不那么容易
not as elegant not as clean
不那么优雅不干净
alternatively one example in MongoDB for
或者在MongoDB中为
example is a tale about queries which
这个例子是关于查询的故事
just works out really nicely right
真的很不错吧
MongoDB is a great example of a Davis
MongoDB是戴维斯的一个很好的例子
driver that is better I think for the
我认为更好的驱动程序
use of reactive programming now I gave
现在我给了反应式编程
you that list of supported reactive
您所支持的反应式列表
database options and you'll you'll note
数据库选项，您会注意到
that I didn't mention a a sequel
我没有提到续集
datastore and that's because up until
数据存储区，这是因为直到
recently there wasn't really a lot of
最近没有很多
good options here a lot of good choices
这里的好选择很多好选择
we had the what I would have to cherub
我们拥有了我所必须的小天使
Lee call an optimistic effort at
李打电话给乐观的努力
supporting asynchronous database access
支持异步数据库访问
in the Oracle a DBA effort announced in
在甲骨文公司宣布的一项DBA工作
that was a almost almost well certainly
那几乎是几乎可以肯定的
more than two years ago right and that
两年多以前
effort has come some ways in the interim
在过渡期间已经付出了一些努力
but it's not anywhere near GA and then
但它不在GA附近，然后
contemporaneous with that well I suppose
我想与那口井同时
subsequent and then contemporaneous with
随后，然后与
that effort is our r2 DBC project and r2
那是我们的r2 DBC项目和r2
BC is an open-source project that we
BC是一个开源项目，我们
have adhere github.com
坚持github.com
r2 DBC is a well
r2 DBC很好
is a reactive relational database
是反应型关系数据库
connectivity API and it is meant to
连接性API，它旨在
provide an SPI what you see here and
提供一个SPI您在这里看到的内容
then several implementations of the SPI
然后是SPI的几种实现
built on where appropriate natively
建立在适当的本机上
reactive or at least natively
反应性的或至少本机的
asynchronous drivers and we then surface
异步驱动程序，然后我们浮出水面
that as as an as an implementation right
作为实施权
a binding if you will and we have to it
如果您愿意，我们将具有约束力
now three interesting bindings they have
现在他们有三个有趣的绑定
PostgreSQL we have h2 and we have just
PostgreSQL我们有h2，我们只有
recently the Microsoft sequel server
最近微软续集服务器
implementation and you know knock on
实施，你知道敲门
wood hopefully there'll be more to come
希望有更多的木头
these are based on actually asynchronous
这些实际上是基于异步的
drivers right different drivers and they
司机对不同的司机，他们
are the first of what we hope will be
是我们希望的第一个
many right we also have a are TBC over a
很多权利，我们也有一个
DBA so if a a DBA ever becomes prolific
DBA，所以如果一个DBA变得多产
and and you know people wanna adapt that
而且你知道人们想要适应
that's fine we expect that our to BC
很好，我们希望我们到卑诗省
will be a a foundational library on top
将成为基础图书馆
of which other things other more
其他还有其他
convenient abstractions will be built
将构建方便的抽象
right in the same way that JDBC is not
就像JDBC不是
something that most people interact with
大多数人都与之互动的东西
directly there's usually some sort of
直接通常有某种
intermediary in there if nothing else
那里的中介
there's something like the JDBC template
就像JDBC模板一样
right which makes work with that lower
正确的，使较低的工作
level spi more palatable so RT BC is if
级别spi更可口，因此RT BC是
nothing else a a a a fundamental
没有别的了
approach at a fundamental take on
基本面的方法
reactive data access for sequel based
基于续集的反应式数据访问
databases it is an SPI and it is a
数据库是一个SPI，它是一个
foundation we wanted to be as
我们想成为的基础
interoperable as possible so if a DBA
尽可能互操作，因此，如果DBA
ever goes anywhere if it becomes useful
如果有用的话，任何地方都可以
we'll be ready um and hey who knows
我们会准备好了，嘿，谁知道
maybe a DBA will become the perfect
也许DBA会变得完美
implementation in which case that would
实施，在那种情况下
hopefully moot the use of our TBC so
希望讨论我们TBC的使用，以便
maybe this would become just a thin
也许这会变得很薄
wrapper on top of that I don't know
我不知道的包装
that's why for the moment at least this
这就是为什么目前至少
is not a recommended for production sort
不建议用于生产排序
of thing but it's certainly interesting
的东西，但肯定很有趣
and I hope you'll consider feeding back
我希望你会考虑反馈
into it we've got a lot of people
里面有很多人
working on this so we certainly hope
为此，我们当然希望
it's info
这是信息
but um you know we're open to being
但是你知道我们很愿意成为
wrong we're open to to having this be
不对，我们愿意接受
just an inspiration right um okay so
只是一个灵感吧，好吧，所以
with that in mind what we're gonna do is
考虑到这一点，我们要做的是
we're gonna use some of this new stuff
我们将使用一些新东西
we're gonna use it directly through our
我们将直接通过我们使用它
TBC and then we're gonna use it through
TBC，然后我们将使用它
a brand new project which is the
一个全新的项目是
reactive analog to yet another new
反应性模拟到另一个新
project both of which we announced that
我们都宣布的项目
spring one platform 2018 the first is
春季一个平台2018年第一个是
spring data JDBC now spring data JDBC is
spring数据JDBC现在spring数据JDBC是
not a new project per se it existed
它本身不是一个新项目
hitherto as a open source community
迄今为止的开源社区
effort that was a separate and apart
分开而分开的努力
from the the the spring you know the
从春天你知道
spring portfolio projects officially
春季投资组合项目正式
from Spring - projects and get up and
从Spring-项目开始
that's a that's a you know a very
那是一个你知道一个非常
interesting effort that's been now
有趣的努力
officially folded into the portfolio of
正式折叠到
projects and I encourage you to take a
项目，我鼓励您参加
look at that for your synchronous and
看看你的同步和
blocking sequel data access needs we
阻止续集数据访问需求
also have spring data r2 DBC which as
也有Spring 数据r2 DBC
you can imagine just as you know just as
你可以想像就知道
with spring data JBC integrates the sort
与 spring data JBC集成了排序
of underlying JDBC or in this case our
基础JDBC或在这种情况下
TBC SPI to provide spring data idioms
TBC SPI提供 spring data 习惯用法
like a template and like a like well in
像模板一样
this case a client and also support for
这种情况下的客户，也支持
repositories so we're gonna take a look
仓库，所以我们来看看
at that when we took a look at both of
当我们同时查看两个
that about those projects RTD BC and
关于那些项目RTD BC和
spring data are TBC in today's
spring data 是今天的TBC
installment of spring tips so in order
安装Spring 头的顺序
to do that we're gonna build a new
为此，我们将建立一个新的
project or two DBC and we're just gonna
一个或两个DBC项目，我们将
use Lombok and I'm gonna use well I
用龙目岛，我会很好用的
suppose that's it I guess that's all I
假设就是这样，我想就是全部
really need to demonstrate everything
真的需要证明一切
we're gonna bring in reactive web just
我们将引入反应式网络
because it's nice to have a reactive web
因为拥有反应性的网站真是太好了
in point I suppose that's easy enough
我想这很容易
but everything else we're gonna have to
但是我们要做的其他一切
add manually so I'm going to I'm going
手动添加，所以我要去
to use the latest in Greater spring boot
使用最新的Greater Spring Boot
and then we're gonna manually change the
然后我们将手动更改
built in other maven build to to have
内置在其他Maven构建中
the appendices that we want
我们想要的附录
already so that's gonna open up and the
已经可以打开了
first thing that we're gonna do is add
我们要做的第一件事是添加
the milestones repository if you haven't
里程碑存储库（如果尚未安装）
already done that if you're not already
已经做到了，如果你还没有
using a milestone version of spring boot
使用Spring Boot的里程碑版本
when you generate the project then
当您生成项目时
you'll you'll want to do that right so
你会想要做的正确的
no steps are to the EBC give me copy and
没有步骤可向EBC抄送给我，
i'm gonna go to my build okay so what do
我要去我的家好，那该怎么办
we got we got those four pot that's the
我们得到了那四个锅
repository that we need I'm gonna put
我们需要的存储库
that in the repositories tag okay paste
在存储库标签中，可以粘贴
that there oh okay face this and these
那里好吧，面对这些
are the dependencies that we need for
是我们需要的依赖
our TBC so paste those in here alright
我们的TBC，所以将它们粘贴在这里
so spring data are 2d BC this is the
所以 spring data 是公元前2d
latest and greatest this was just
最新最好的
announced about a week ago and here's
大约一个星期前宣布，这是
our TBC postgrads this is the driver for
我们的TBC研究生，这是
Postgres and as I said there are a
Postgres，正如我所说，有一个
couple of versions this is the one that
这是几个版本
I know to work well with swing data or
我知道可以很好地处理挥杆数据或
TBC so we use that and in our code we're
TBC，所以我们用它，在我们的代码中
gonna start with low level or 2d BC in
将以低水位或公元前2d开始
order to do that in order to start any
为了做到这一点，以开始任何
of this effort we need a connection
为此，我们需要一个连接
factory don't we need to actually have a
工厂不是，我们实际上需要一个
connection to a Postgres database so I
连接到Postgres数据库，所以我
am gonna build a connection factory
我要建立一个连接工厂
configuration and again I expect that
配置，我再次期望
this will be one of those things that's
这将是
best handled for us
最适合我们的
by spring boot one day hopefully soon
到 spring boot ，希望很快有一天
rather than later and a spring boot
而不是后来的 spring boot
could Auto configure the connection
可以自动配置连接
factory just as it Auto configure the
自动配置
data source for us today Ryan so I'm
今天我们的数据源瑞安，所以我
gonna you know fingers crossed that'll
你会知道手指交叉那会
be a thing we can enjoy in the future
成为我们将来可以享受的东西
now a very natural thing to do would be
现在要做的很自然的事情是
to you know knowing that spring boot
知道那 spring boot
will one day probably support it and
有一天可能会支持它，并且
will probably do so in a way that's
可能会以
familiar and some you know compatible
熟悉并且您知道一些兼容
with what we're already doing you could
利用我们已经在做的事情，您可以
put your connection string your York to
将您的连接字符串放入York
do BC connection string and a spring
做BC连接线和Spring
data source that URL and then inject
数据源，然后输入URL
that into your code somewhere manually
手动输入到您的代码中
so as to you know you would you'd
以至于你知道你会
actually inject it using a property like
实际上使用诸如
so add value
所以增加价值
and you know spring data source that URL
而且您知道Spring数据源该URL
string URL okay so that's one option you
字符串网址好，所以这是您的一种选择
could do I'm just gonna hard code my
我能做的只是硬编码我的
username and password here I don't care
我不在乎用户名和密码
I've got it in my local machine
我已经在我的本地机器上了
you'd have to unit if you were injecting
如果要注射，就必须团结
that that connection string you'd have
您将拥有的连接字符串
to pick apart the information and you
挑选信息，你
know I trust you can do that just use
知道我相信你可以做到这一点
the java net URI I under the hand I'm
我手下的java net URI
gonna do this the old-fashioned way
会用老式的方式
we're gonna return a new connection
我们将返回一个新的连接
factory and this requires some
工厂，这需要一些
configuration the config object we're
配置我们的配置对象
going to extract out into a local
要提取到本地
variable there and it'll say Postgres
那里的变量，它会说Postgres
connection factory build it up build I'm
连接工厂建立它建立我
gonna say dot builder dot database
要说点构建器点数据库
orders password pass what password the
命令密码通过什么密码
orders ORS okay username orders and
订单ORS好的用户名订单和
that's yeah I think database host
是的，我认为数据库主机
localhost okay and that should be it
本地主机好，应该是这样
that's the configuration for the
这是配置
connection factory now for now that'll
现在连接工厂
get us started that'll give us a basic
让我们开始，这将给我们一个基本的
r2 DBC machinery we might also want a
r2 DBC机械，我们可能还需要一个
database client that works with that and
与之兼容的数据库客户端
the database client is a is a object
数据库客户端是一个对象
that that supports reactive data access
支持反应式数据访问
through our TBC and it's sort of like
通过我们的TBC，有点像
the the analog to the JDBC template and
JDBC模板的类似物，以及
they reactive world you notice that
他们反应的世界，你注意到
we've we've moved in certain cases from
在某些情况下，我们已经从
template objects to client objects so in
模板对象到客户端对象，因此
the reactive web domain we've got the
反应性网络域，我们已经
spring webflix project and then there we
spring webflix项目，然后在那里
have a web client rather than a rest
有一个网络客户端，而不是休息
template right and now we have the
模板，现在我们有了
database client inside of the JDBC
JDBC内部的数据库客户端
template so that's you know kind of a
模板，这样您就知道了
new thing okay now we need that database
好了，现在我们需要该数据库
client so that here
客户在这里
and here we can just use the Builder
在这里我们可以使用Builder
just as before connection factory there
就像连接工厂之前一样
we are now we'll see later that we can
我们现在我们稍后会看到我们可以
actually comment that out later but for
实际上稍后再评论
now we're okay now what I want to do is
现在我们可以了，我想做的是
want to build an application that works
想要构建一个可以运行的应用程序
with and manages entities of type
与并管理类型的实体
reservation can you imagine and my
您可以想象的预订和我的
reservation is fairly familiar you've
您已经很熟悉预订
seen this a million times I'm sure if
我看过一百万次
you've ever seen my talks so ID private
您曾经看过我的演讲，所以ID为私人
integer ID private string we're just
我们只是整数ID私有字符串
gonna call this name alright so there's
会叫这个名字好，所以
my thing that's gonna be using Lombok to
我要用龙目岛的东西
create the getters and setters good ok
创建吸气剂和二传手很好
there's my three fields and from there
有我的三个领域，从那里
we're gonna read some data to the davis
我们要读一些数据给戴维斯
i'm gonna create a repository manually
我要手动创建一个存储库
here i'm gonna do this the old-fashioned
在这里，我要去做老式的
way we're gonna write our our sequel by
我们要写我们的续集的方式
hand i know
我知道的手
gasps but um the benefit is that we can
喘着粗气，但好处是我们可以
see some of the low-level RVT CSPI or
查看一些低级RVT CSPI或
api and if and it really isn't so bad
api，如果它的确不是那么糟糕
it's actually quite approachable
实际上很平易近人
certainly as approachable if not more
当然可以平易近人
than regular JDBC which you know about
比您所了解的常规JDBC
us so what it does does does a fine job
我们，所以它所做的工作做得很好
as well so no need to know need to be
同样，所以无需知道需要
sour on either I've always been a big
我一直都很胖
JDBC fan now as you know from some of
如您所知，JDBC粉丝现在
the other videos we've done in the
我们在其中完成的其他视频
spring tip series we've done videos that
春季秘诀系列，我们制作了一些视频，
looked at my betas for example and we
例如看我的beta
looked at hibernate and we looked at a
看着冬眠，我们看着
Jo Java or Q you know the Duke project
Jo Java或Q，您知道Duke项目
so lots of different efforts to support
有很多不同的努力来支持
and make easier the work of using JDBC
并简化使用JDBC的工作
but ultimately I think JDBC is pretty
但最终我认为JDBC很漂亮
powerful okay so we've got this and of
强大，好的，所以我们已经有了
course I know the videos we've even
我当然知道我们的影片
looked at the JDBC template I've done a
看着JDBC模板，我做了一个
couple of videos looking at cloud
几个看云的视频
platforms actually and there I
平台在那里，我
introduced how to talk to a sequel
介绍了如何与续集对话
database in terms of the JDBC template
JDBC模板方面的数据库
because why not
因为为什么不
so here we have a reservation repository
所以在这里我们有一个预订库
and the suppository is going to support
栓剂将支持
a few of the usual things it will
一些通常的事情
support a delete
支持删除
by IE I suppose gonna be an integer ID
通过IE，我想将是一个整数ID
okay we'll come back to that and it'll
好吧，我们将回到这一点，它将
support a we just support returning a
支持我们只支持返回一个
publisher of reservation like so okay
预订的发布者这样还行
and it'll support returning a saved
并且将支持返回保存的
reservation okay I'll come back to that
保留好，我会再说一遍
alright so I think and we want to delete
好吧，我想，我们想删除
by ID we've got to find all and we've
通过ID，我们必须找到全部，并且
got to save okay so now let's just
必须保存好，所以现在让我们
implement Wendy's and I suppose we could
实施温迪的，我想我们可以
start with the the more fun one which is
从更有趣的一个开始
like to find all I always love doing
喜欢找到我一直喜欢做的一切
queries because you know who wants to
查询，因为您知道谁想要
put data there it's much more fun to
将数据放到那里更有趣
read it out and to work with it so um
读出来并与之一起使用
we'll start with that I'm gonna need a
我们将开始，我需要一个
connection okay so I'm gonna need a
连接好，所以我需要一个
connection to be able to do this so I'm
连接才能做到这一点，所以我
gonna vend a connection here and I'm
要在这里建立联系，我
just gonna have a little hot finder
只会有一个小发现者
method here a little convenient method
方法这里有点方便
private mono connection okay and here
私人单声道连接还可以，这里
mono dot from this connection factory
此连接工厂的单点
dot create okay so this might publish my
点创建好，所以这可能会发布我的
pop by my connection when I say this
当我说这话时，我的连接就弹出了
start connection
开始连接
and what I want to do is I want to find
我想做的就是找到
all the results I'm gonna say lift the
我要说的所有结果都解除了
connection let's process the data and go
连接让我们处理数据并继续
through the results so flux dive from
通过结果，流量从
connection dot create statement select
连接点创建语句选择
all from reservation ok
全部来自保留好
and we're going to execute that query
我们将执行该查询
and with that with that oops
和那个哎呀
one flat map mini from this done execute
从此完成一个迷你地图
dot flat map ok
点平面图确定
we're gonna have a row and what we're
我们要去吵一架，我们要
gonna do is I'm gonna say row dot map
我要说的是行点图
and this is kind of the roll mapperton
这就是卷起马普顿
to G GTP's template Road up map I guess
到G GTP的模板Road up map我猜
we can just call this R for ease of
我们可以简称为R
dereferencing and when we have that
取消引用，当我们拥有
we're gonna lambda so it's gonna be row
我们要lambda，所以要排
and row metadata to be metadata about
和行元数据是关于的元数据
the row and we're gonna process all of
该行，我们将处理所有
that and turned into a object so Rho dot
然后变成了一个物体，所以Rho dot
again does this look fairly familiar
再次看起来很熟悉
this should look like the row mapper if
这应该看起来像行映射器，如果
you ever use the row member and JDBC
您曾经使用过行成员和JDBC
template where we give it a pointer to
我们给它一个指针的模板
the current result set and the current
当前结果集和当前
offset right the index on in the result
向右偏移结果上的索引
set very similar to the row mapper
设置与行映射器非常相似
contract in JDBC template in spring
春季在JDBC模板中签约
Springs regular JDBC support but this is
Springs常规的JDBC支持，但这是
I think wiser for all the sort of use
我认为所有用途都比较明智
cases that with which people are might
人们可能会遇到的情况
might have become a familiar over here
在这里可能已经很熟悉了
so here we're gonna return an integer
所以这里我们要返回一个整数
duck class for the ID and when we turn a
鸭子类的ID，当我们打开一个
road I could get name that's gonna
我能得到的名字的路
string that class okay
串那个课好吗
so what's happening here we're saying
所以我们在说什么
when somebody makes a connection use the
当有人建立联系时使用
connection and take and when we have the
连接和采取，当我们有
connection we want to create a result
我们要创建结果的连接
tip from that all right we're gonna
提示，好的，我们要
execute this and that'll give us a
执行这个，那会给我们一个
publisher of results and then with each
结果发布者，然后与每个
result that we get back we're gonna
结果我们回来了
flatmap the results because it's
将结果平面化，因为它是
reactive it's a publisher so I'm gonna
反应性的是出版商，所以我要
do you reference e we're gonna unpack
你参考我们要打开包装吗
the intermediate publisher and then
中间发布者，然后
visit the results themselves and so for
自己访问结果，因此
each result for each result are like
每个结果每个结果都像
this for each RTP see results are we're
这对于每个RTP来说，结果都是
gonna map the result given the row and
给定行映射结果，然后
the row metadata into a reservation
将行元数据转换为保留
object I'm going to do that by unpacking
对象，我将通过拆包来做到这一点
the relevant columns in the read and the
阅读和
result object into the constructor of my
结果对象放入我的构造函数中
new reservation and the result of that
新的保留及其结果
will of course be a flux of reservation
当然将是保留的潮流
right that's that's the contract here so
对，这就是这里的合同，所以
that is fairly straightforward right
那是相当简单的权利
we're just just reactively row mapping
我们只是反应式的行映射
the data which I love okay
我喜欢的数据
we want to then save some data so let's
我们想要保存一些数据，所以让
see in order to save a reservation we
看到为了保存预订我们
want to say that we want to say this but
想说我们想说这个，但是
connection dot black map mini and what
连接点黑色地图迷你和什么
we're gonna do is we're gonna say given
我们要去做，我们要说给定
the con create a statement and when
骗局创建一个声明，以及何时
insert into reservation name values
插入预订名称值
waterside one now dollar sign one is the
水边一现在美元符号之一是
it's the way we bind in spring data or
这是我们在spring数据中绑定的方式
to DBC and our CBC in general so when I
到DBC和我们的CBC，所以当我
say bind dollar sign one see get our
说绑定美元符号一个看到得到我们
don't get name okay and I'm gonna add
不要叫好名字，我要加​​上
this to the database I'm gonna execute
这到我要执行的数据库
right so what does that give us that
是的，那给我们带来了什么
gives us
给我们
this gives us a publisher of results and
这使我们成为结果的发布者，并且
then we're just gonna switch we're gonna
然后我们要切换
map each one of those and rent it out
绘制每个地图并出租
okay so there's our data you know we can
好，所以有我们的数据，您知道我们可以
actually just say return plat map mini
其实只是说return plat map mini
got to switch map I suppose and return
我必须切换地图，然后返回
our and just return a publisher let's
我们并返回一个发布者，让我们
just do that for now okay new
现在就做吧好吧新
reservation our duck get IP oh thanks
预订我们的鸭子获得IP哦，谢谢
name all right
好吧名字
there we go there's our save that's
我们去那里有我们的保存
pretty straightforward what else well we
很简单，我们还有什么
need to do a delete by 80 don't Lea so
需要在80之前删除，所以不要这样
here this start connection this one's
在这里这个开始连接这个
easy this one we just say flatmap many
这个简单，我们只说平面图很多
see and I'm gonna say C dot great
看，我要说C点很棒
statement delete from reservation where
声明从保留位置删除
ID equals 1 and we're gonna bind dot 1
ID等于1，我们将绑定点1
to ID we're gonna say execute and then
到ID，我们要说执行然后
we'll sit then give us a mono avoid
我们坐下来然后给我们一个单声道避免
simple as it can be okay so those are
很简单，因为可以，所以这些
our simple repository we've got the
我们的简单存储库
entity we've got a connection factory
实体，我们有一个连接工厂
that's all we need for regular are TBC
这就是我们需要的常规TBC
now let's go ahead and test this code
现在让我们继续测试此代码
that's actually write a bit of code just
那实际上只是写一些代码
to exercise this and so we're gonna do
锻炼这个，所以我们要做
is want to create a reservation
要创建预订
repository test over here
此处的存储库测试
okay I'm gonna use the reactor context
好吧，我要使用反应堆环境
test support okay so we'll say spring
测试支持好吧，我们就说春天
boot test run with spring runner class
使用SpringRunner类进行引导测试运行
okay and I'm gonna inject the
好吧，我要注入
reservation apposite story like so
预订像这样的故事
create a test public void all doing
创建一个测试公众无效
just to really test everything probably
只是为了真正测试一切
a bad test but it we just want to
一个不好的测试，但我们只想
demonstrate everything's working so
证明一切正常
let's say this that reservation applause
假设这是预订的掌声
joy dot find all thought flatmap are the
欢乐点找到所有以为平面图是
stock reservation positive delete by ID
库存预订正按ID删除
r dot get ID so I'm I'm now testing that
r点获取ID，所以我现在正在测试
okay that's one thing I want to verify
好，那是我要验证的一件事
that that works I'll use a step verifier
可行的方法，我将使用步骤验证器
I'll say a crate delete our void flux
我会说一个板条箱删除了我们的空洞通量
that'll be called that but I'm gonna
那会叫那个，但我要
rename it to delete all ok dot expect
重命名以删除所有预期的OK点
next count will be let's say zero that
下一个计数将为零
verify complete good and then we're
验证完好，然后我们
gonna say I want to write some data to
要说我想写一些数据到
the Devi so I'll say luck start just I'm
Devi，所以我会说运气开始
gonna write some emails let's say or
要写一些电子邮件，例如
just names I guess so first second third
只是名字，我猜所以第一，第二，第三
and then I'm gonna map each one of those
然后我要映射每个
names into a new reservation know name
名称进入新的预订知道名称
I'm gonna map each one of those into a
我要把每个人都映射到一个
written data save are okay there we go
书面数据保存可以
and I want to verify that we have the
我想确认我们有
expected amount in the database
数据库中的预期数量
count is three there if I complete great
如果我完成得很好，那里是三
and then finally I want to get all the
最后我想得到所有
data and can just confirm that it's
数据，只需确认它是
working as we expected it to so not all
像我们期望的那样工作
good there's that and we're gonna say
好，就是这样，我们要说
step verifier dot-com I create all that
我创建了所有步骤验证器dot-com
expect the next count three verify
期待下一次计数三验证
complete there we go there's all three
完成那里，我们去了所有三个
of them very simple those are three
其中非常简单的是三个
methods in you know being exercised a
你知道被锻炼的方法
little bit here I suppose I could have
我想我可以在这里一点
extracted these out in two separate
将它们分别提取出来
tests but I'm trying to see that'll work
测试，但我试图看到它会工作
so let's go ahead and hit run with what
所以让我们继续前进
we've got we should be okay
我们有我们应该没事的
oops semicolons are required this isn't
哎呀分号是必需的，这不是
Cartman after all
毕竟卡特曼
Dubi Dubi work come on here we go
Dubi Dubi工作来了，我们继续
cool that work that's green I suppose I
我想我酷的是绿色的工作
should show you the database right I so
应该给你看数据库吧
P sequel - you orders orders
P续集-您订购订单
you know I'll need let's try it again
你知道我需要让我们再试一次
from reservation I mean I got rid of
从保留我的意思是我摆脱了
three records there we're gonna run the
三个记录，我们要运行
test again
再次测试
okay select all from reservation and
好吧，从预订中选择所有
there we go so there's our records right
我们去了，所以我们的记录是正确的
so that's working that's fine that's
这样就可以了那很好
that's basic our two DBC very low-level
这是我们两个DBC非常底层的基础
but not so bad I think it's very
但还不错，我认为这非常
functional it's really clean really easy
功能真的很干净很容易
to work with
跟...共事
and that's great now we need to go a
太好了，我们现在需要
step further don't we we need to go step
再走一步，我们需要走一步
further so let's now use the spring data
更进一步，让我们现在使用spring数据
or two BC projects what I'm gonna do is
或两个卑诗省项目我要做的是
I'm gonna comment out this repository
我要评论这个仓库
helpful though it's been easy enough and
很有帮助，尽管已经很容易了
succinct enough though it is we're gonna
虽然足够简洁，但我们要
comment that out I'm gonna use spring
评论说我要用Spring
data are to BC and that will make our
数据是送往卑诗省的，这将使我们
life significantly easier right as
生活明显容易了
though it weren't easy enough somehow so
尽管以某种方式还不容易
I'm gonna leave this here this is fine
我要离开这里，这很好
but we don't actually need this and I'm
但是我们实际上并不需要这个
just gonna create another configuration
只是要创建另一个配置
class but there's no reason that it
上课，但没有理由
couldn't be the same you know or in the
可能与您认识的不一样
main configuration class extends
主要配置类扩展
abstract are 2d BC when I override this
当我覆盖此时，抽象是2d BC
method the connection factor method in
方法中的连接因子方法
order to provide that response then
为了提供那个回应
we're just injecting the connection
我们只是注入连接
factor that we've already created into
我们已经创造的因素
the constructor I always say return this
我经常说的构造函数返回
dot connection factory I'm gonna say at
点连接工厂我要说的
configuration that enabled Archie vc+
启用Archie vc +的配置
alright so there's that that's the hard
好吧，那就是很难
work that we have to do we need to
我们需要做的工作
annotate our thing our entity it's got
注释我们的东西我们的实体
ID so we're already halfway home and
ID，所以我们已经中途回家了
then we need to create a new repository
然后我们需要创建一个新的存储库
no way so we can do that pretty easily
没办法，所以我们可以很容易地做到这一点
we can say interface reservation
我们可以说接口保留
repository extends reactive crud
存储库扩展了反应堆
repository managing reservations whose
存储库管理其预订
primary keys of type integer and that's
类型为整数的主键，即
it that's it that's the configuration
这就是配置
part ABC we need that for the moment
部分ABC，我们目前需要
hopefully in one day and in the
希望在一天之内
far-flung future the auto configured I
遥不可及的未来，自动配置的
mean this is not really hard at this
意思是说这并不难
point right but um it's still code that
说对了，但是它仍然是代码
I can easily imagine spring boot doing
我可以轻松想象 spring boot 在做什么
form
形成
so that I can just create this interface
这样我就可以创建这个界面
in this entity and be on my way we can
在这个实体上，在我的路上，我们可以
go back to our test
回到我们的测试
alright how's that so I'm we did good
好吧那怎么样，所以我我们做得很好
look at that huh
看那个吧
there's our simple test everything's
有一个简单的测试，一切都是
working just fine you know we can we
工作很好，你知道我们可以
should have let me delete the data just
应该让我删除数据
in case there's that run that again
万一有再次运行
look here we go so there's our data so
看这里，我们走了，所以有我们的数据，所以
you can see that this is a nice easy way
您会看到这是一个很好的简便方法
to get a reactive sequel base for
得到一个反应性的续集基础
positive obviously this is a you know
积极显然这是你知道的
you can create custom queries as well so
您也可以创建自定义查询
I could say find all the reservations by
我可以说找到所有的保留
name string name right it doesn't
名称字符串名称正确，不是
support auto derivation of queries based
支持基于查询的自动派生
on the method names yet
在方法名称上
so in order to do that you'd have to say
因此，为了做到这一点，您必须说
add query select all from reservation
添加查询从预订中全选
where name post one right and then we
名字在哪儿发表，然后我们
can actually test that out here we could
可以在这里实际测试
actually now say this dot reservation
实际上现在说这个点保留
repository I find by name and the name
我通过名称和名称找到存储库
would be first and assert that'll give
将是第一个并断言会给
us a result result I'm gonna say find
我们一个结果，我要说找到
the first we're gonna expect one to come
首先我们要期待一个
back and then verify its complete okay
返回，然后验证其是否完全正常
so that's our our custom query let's see
这就是我们的自定义查询
what that looks like
看起来像什么
all right not bad huh so we were able to
好的还不错吧，所以我们能够
get when we walked back we found the one
当我们走回去时，我们找到了一个
we thought we expected this makes life
我们以为我们期望这可以使生活
easier now we have a long ways to go I
容易，现在我们还有很长的路要走
think before this is all like you know
想想这一切就像你知道的那样
this solves every problem for everybody
这为每个人解决了所有问题
of course it's not gonna be tomorrow but
当然不是明天了
there's a lot of interesting
有很多有趣的事情
possibilities here you can now do
您现在可以在这里做的可能性
reactive sequel based data access we get
我们获得基于反应性续集的数据访问
the benefits of reactive programming one
反应式编程的好处之一
thing is one thing that's you know kind
一件事是你知道的一种
of interesting is to watch the
有趣的是看
interoperability options here we can
我们可以在此处选择互操作性
actually there are projects out there
其实那里有项目
that are aiming to support integrating
旨在支持整合
for example Zipkin and distribute racing
例如Zipkin并分发赛车
and micrometer for from metrics
和千分尺
accumulation with these projects right
与这些项目积累权利
there's already connection pools that
已经有连接池了
are being developed support this I mean
正在开发支持我的意思是
there's all sorts of interesting stuff
有各种各样有趣的东西
happening in and and beyond the artists
在艺术家内外发生
unique projects and the ecosystem that
独特的项目和生态系统
is created around that
围绕它创建
so let me interesting to see where this
所以让我很有趣地看看
goes I think this API is really
我认为这个API确实是
convenient
方便
I like the rgbc API by itself I like the
我本身喜欢rgbc API，也喜欢
reactive Spring data our TBC support as
我们的TBC支持的反应性Spring数据为
well and you can see I was able to just
好吧，你可以看到我能够
drop in I just comment that out just
落入我只是评论出来
added the ID annotation and a table I
添加了ID注释和一个表I
had to create this boilerplate
必须创建这个样板
configuration here but this is not a big
在这里配置，但这不是很大
deal so really the the full footprint of
真正做到了
the code that you know the mental
你知道的代码
overhead that I had to pay and I even
我必须支付的开销，我什至
got I got all that stuff I did for free
得到我免费得到的所有东西
I did that I got that same thing I got I
我做到了我得到的同样的东西
got to find all the tallit and all this
必须找到所有的tallit和所有这一切
if I got that for free and I got this
如果我免费得到，我得到了
new method which is a custom query which
新方法，这是一个自定义查询
Maps my slate to this parameter with
使用以下命令将我的平板映射到此参数
almost no no effort at all right no
几乎没有没有努力没有
mapping no no queuing up a connection or
映射否否排队或
anything like that so I I like this
像这样的东西
approach I hope you like it too
我希望你也喜欢
and obviously this is a very natural fit
显然这是非常自然的契合
with spring webflix so if you wanted to
用spring webflix，所以如果你想
create a state reactive end in from the
从创建一个状态反应端
database loop tear all the way to the
数据库循环一直撕到
web tier and through the security layer
Web层并通过安全层
and all that stuff and back again you
还有所有这些东西，然后又回来
could do that now you can actually have
现在就可以做到
a spring web flux endpoint that we that
Spring 腹板通量端点
served up this data and also you could
提供了这些数据，您也可以
use this in conjunction with our socket
与我们的插座一起使用
the the the the protocol developed by
由开发的协议
Facebook that supports reactive
支持反应性的Facebook
interoperability it's a wire protocol
互操作性是有线协议
that has an
有一个
at the moment at least three different
目前至少三个不同
clients went in C++ when in JavaScript
客户端使用JavaScript时使用C ++
and of course one in Java
当然是Java中的一个
powered by reactor and you can use that
由电抗器提供动力，您可以使用
to you know fire and forget
要知道火就忘了
request/response pub/sub and full
请求/响应发布/订阅和完整
bi-directional multiplexing and
双向复用和
streaming I mean you could all sorts of
流媒体，我的意思是你可以各种各样
interesting things and there's built-in
有趣的东西，并且内置
support at the protocol level for
在协议级别支持
communicating availability so you can
传达可用性，以便您可以
use this you know technologies like r2
使用这个，你会知道像r2这样的技术
DBC and spring that are two DBC with
DBC和spring是两个DBC
technologies like our socket and with
像我们的插座和
technologies like spring web flex to get
像Spring Web Flex这样的技术
a completely intend reactive stack you
一个完全打算的反应堆
know on what we might have thought of as
了解我们可能想到的
being sort of traditional api's all
有点像传统的api
right so my friends thanks so much for
是的，所以我的朋友们非常感谢
that I hope you got something out of
我希望你从中得到一些东西
this as hot as always thanks for
一如既往的热烈感谢
watching and we'll see you next time
看，下次见
you
您